

PEDRO SASTRE

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birth date: 19/10/95 Nationality: Argentina

Phone number: +5411-3645-3576 E-Mail: pedro2000sastre@gmail.com

Address: Retiro, CABA

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pedro-

sastre-64b72618b/

GitHub: https://github.com/psastre

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer with experienced in teamwork and problem solving under pressure.

This experience was with a team of 5 people, taking, organizing and managing 100 orders per day, from customers, and passing them on to professional technicians, and trying to reach an agreement against any claim from the two parties.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Development

StartUp | 2021

Design and animation development for e-commerce web application. HTML, CSS, JavaScript were used for interactions and validations, and GSAP for animations. With responsive design adapted for any device. Project on hold for the moment, waiting back-end development for deploying.

Link: https://proyecto-pique.firebaseapp.com/

Website front-end and newsletter manager

Soluciones Hogar | 2019 - 2021

Intermediary company between professionals and clients in home repair services.

- Website maintenance.
- Management of social networks, (content creation and account management)

Communication and customer service manager

Soluciones Hogar | 2014 - 2019

- Organization of telephone assistance.
- Resolutions in the claims area.

ACADEMIC TRAINING

THREE.JS course

August 2021 - November 2021 | Chris Courses

React and Redux course

January 2021 - February 2021 | Developed by Ed

Full Stack development course

HTML - CSS - PHP - JavaScript

February 2018 - July 2018 | Digital house

Degree in advertising

Development of communication strategy, and media planning.

Study of brands, ideas and creative concepts for advertising campaigns.

2015 - 2019 | UADE

SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

-HTML -MySQL
-CSS -Bootstrap
-Javascript -GSAP
-React -SVG
-Hooks -Sass
-Redux -VSCode
-Api Rest -Figma

-PHP -English: Advanced Level

-Laravel -Portuguese: Intermediate level